# Dao Duc Tai

+84 868930418 - Portfolio - daotai.work@gmail.com - linkedin.com/in/dao-tai-61757325a - github.com/DaoTai

## **SUMMARY**

I am a web developer with approximately 2 years of experience in web programming on the NodeJS platform. Additionally, I have basic knowledge of the JavaScript programming language and Object-Oriented Programming (OOP). My target is to become a good skill programmer in the future and I am willing to learn new knowledge to serve job requirements.

#### **EDUCATION**

## ThuyLoi University

Ha Noi, Viet Nam

Bachelor of Engineering In Information Technology

Aug 2019 - Apr 2024

**GPA:** 8/10

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

**Programming languages:** HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript. **Frameworks and libraries:** NextJS, ReactJS, NestJS, ExpressJS.

Technologies: Socket, WebRTC, JWT, Redux, TailwindCSS, Material UI, Mongoose, MongoDB Driver.

**Tools:** Git, Postman, Swagger, Figma. **Database:** NoSQL (MongoDB).

# WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Fullstack Developer**

Bwai Tech Feb 2024 - Apr 2024

- Develop web applications with technologies in NodeJS platform like NextJS, NestJS, ReactJS, ExpressJS.
- Convert and build UI from Figma templates.
- · Work collaboratively and manage source code by Git.

#### Frontend Intern

USOL VietNam

Jun 2023 - Aug 2023

- Joined to train and develop a software project with professional Japanese workflow.
- Become team leader consists of 3 members.
- Collaborate and work with team members to build user interfaces and integrate API from backend.
- Used technologies: NextJS, Material UI, Tailwind CSS, Redux Toolkit, SVN.

## **PROJECTS**

## VAN THANH DOCTOR'S CLINIC

Bwai Tech Mar 2024 - Apr 2024

- Role: Fullstack developer. In this project, I am responsible for designing database, developing for the admin website as well as update main website.
- Technologies: NextJS, ReactJS, ReduxToolkit, ShadcnUI (Tailwind Css), Zod, React hook form, NestJS, MongoDB, JWT, Cloudinary, Swagger, Postman, Git, Figma.
- Summary: It is a website introducing the clinic as well as displaying and search posts, banner images, a list of experts, and other information. Additionally, the administrator page will manage data the system by authentication.
- Public link: https://phongkhambacsyvanthanh.com

## **BWAI TECH WEBSITE**

Bwai Tech Feb 2024 - Mar 2024

- Role: Fullstack developer. My work is design UI, database and developing for the admin website as well as update main website.
- Technologies: NextJS, Tailwind Css, Yup, Formik, ExpressJS, Joi, Cloudinary, MongoDB, Postman, Git.
- Summary: The main features are introduce information of Bwai Tech company like products, classes, recruitments, videos. Finally, the administrator page will manage data of system by authentication.
- Public link: https://bwaitech.com

## **EST EDU**

Private project Sep 2023 - Jan 2024

• Role: Fullstack developer. It is my private project so I design UI, database and build front-end, back-end as well as develop AI feature by LSTM network.

- Technologies: NextJS, Material UI, Tailwind Css, NextAuth, SocketIo, Simple Peer (WebRTC), ExpressJS, JWT Nodemailer, Cloudinary, MongoDB, Flask API, Numpy, Pandas, Keras.
- Summary: It is a web app to learn programming courses. The functionalities are built to serve administrator, teachers, and users, enabling them to manage courses, lectures, exercises, comments, and personal account, etc. Additionally, they can communicate via text messaging and online video calls using Socket and WebRTC technologies. Finally, users can predict suitable fields of study through data such as scores, courses, etc., using LSTM networks.
- Public link: https://est-edu.vercel.app
- Video demo: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KkbwgK8uYDw

#### **SOCIAL MEDIA**

Private project Jan 2023 - Mar 2023

- Role: Fullstack developer. It is my private project so I design UI, database and build both front-end and back-end
- Technologies: ReactJS, Material UI, SocketIo, Redux, Redux Saga, ExpressJS, JWT, Nodemailer, Cloudinary, Firebase, MongoDB.
- Summary: It is a social media web app which is similar to Facebook. Users can upload their images, posts, comments and chat with friends. Finally, administrator can manage and authorize account.